Guide to the NURTUREart records CBHM.0025
Center for Brooklyn History
NURTUREart records
1997-2019
Center for Brooklyn History
NURTUREart
CBHM.0025
42.3 Linear feet in 84 manuscript boxes, 3 cartons, 3 flat boxes, and 1 1/2 manuscript box.
NURTUREart records document the gallery's exhibitions, programs, and administrative activities from its founding in 1997 to its closure in 2019. Items include artists' registry submissions, board minutes, fundraising documents, and materials from the Education Outreach Program and Emerging Curators' Program. Exhibit files include press releases, promotional materials, agreements and contracts, photographs, slides, sales documents, correspondence, contact information, and artist submissions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in 4 series by topic. See series level notes for a full description.
Historical Note
NURTUREart was founded in 1997 by former art dealer George J. Robinson as an organization dedicated to providing exhibition space for emerging artists. Early shows were staged at the United Nations, Presbyterian Hospital, and empty storefronts. NURTUREart also maintained an artists' slide registry, held in a filing cabinet in Robinson's Washington Heights apartment. Muse Fuse, a monthly networking event for artists on the registry, became a popular salon style event featuring guest speakers, hosted by board member Karen Marston in her studio for over ten seasons.
In 2002, NURTUREart expanded programming to include the Emerging Curators Program, which facilitated introductions and collaborations between curators and artists to create mutually advantageous growth possibilities. In 2003, NURTUREart opened a dedicated gallery at 475 Keap Street in Williamsburg, which allowed for a full season of rotating exhibitions and a growing budget that provided stipends to participating artists and curators. The slide registry, expanding to over 1500 artists, was digitized and launched online.
In 2005, board member and teaching artist Eliot Lable founded NURTUREarts' Education Outreach Program with 9th graders at the neighboring Juan Morel Campos Secondary School. The program quickly expanded to include hundreds of students from local schools, taught by artists and curators in residence. Students followed a curriculum focusing on art history, artmaking, curating, discussing art, and critiquing art. One of the most popular programs, Project Curate, guided students through the process of curating their own exhibits, from selecting artists to installing the work at the NURTUREart gallery. Popular Project Curate shows included Juxtacombo (2012), #Artistsbelike (2013), and (Im)Perfection (2019).
In 2006, George Robinson retired, replaced by Karen Marston. The gallery also moved to a new space at 910 Grand Street in Williamsburg, then in 2011 to its final location at 56 Bogart Street in Bushwick. In addition to its regular exhibit season, NURTUREart held both general fundraising events and shows offsite featuring work donated by artists, the sales of which benefited the gallery, including the popular Nurturing the New (2005) and Nurturing the Edge (2006). The gallery also secured funding from individual donors, grants, and a portion of the gallery's sales.¹
In 2019, NURTUREart closed citing "confluence of resource challenges and a shifting environment for non-profits." During its 22 years NURTUREart presented 17 full seasons of 6-8 exhibitions in addition to numerous curatorial projects at guest locations around New York City. Its online registry promoted the work of 2,100 emerging artists and curators. Its Education Outreach Program sent 161 artists and 11 curators to teach 1,170 public school students in four schools in Brooklyn. The education programs also provided exhibition opportunities for 80 artists in 35 exhibitions and events.²
1. Source: Adapted from the organizational history provided by NURTUREart at the time of accession.
2. Source: Bishara, H. (2019, June 21). NURTUREart, a Veteran Brooklyn Nonprofit Gallery, is Closing. Hyperallergic. https://hyperallergic.com/506326/nurtureart-a-veteran-brooklyn-nonprofit-gallery-is-closing/.
Conditions Governing Access
Due to sensitive personal information some folders in Series 4: Education are restricted until 2075. All other records are open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Carol Salmanson, 2021.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The majority of the materials in this collection are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact cbhreference@bklynlibrary.org at least two weeks prior to research visit.
VHS tapes are unavailable due to technical limitations.
If digital surrogates exist, they should be used in place of the originals whenever possible.
Related Materials
Center for Brooklyn History holds the following related collections:
Brooklyn Arts Council Folk Arts collection (CBHM.0002)
Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association publications (ARC.149)
Brooklyn Film and Arts Festival Collection (BCMS.0033)
Brooklyn Society of Artists records (1997.080)
Scope and Contents
NURTUREart records document the gallery's exhibitions, programs, and administrative activities from its founding in 1997 to its closure in 2019. The bulk of the collection is composed artist submissions, held in Series 1: Artists' Registry. Items in Series 2: Exhibits includes examples of artwork submitted for exhibits, inventories, sales documents, promotional materials, and contracts. With few exceptions, the artwork held in series 1 and 2 are copies reproduced on computer or photo paper.
Series 3: Administrative records holds materials created in the day-to-day management of the gallery and staff inlcuding board minutes (1998-2019), oganizational documents, fundraising efforts, and marketing informaiton. Series 4: Education includes materials created by students and NURTUREart staff as part of NURTUREarts' Education Outreach Program.
See series level notes for full descriptions.
Art -- Collectors and collecting -- United States; Art, American -- 21st century; Art, American -- 20th century; Art -- Exhibitions; Bushwick (New York, N.Y.); American artists -- United States; Administrative records; Nonprofit organizations -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Exhibition records; Photographic prints; Sales records; Flyers (printed matter); Résumés (personnel records); submissions (visual works)
- Series 1: Artists' Registry
  Arrangement
  Series 1: Artists' Registry is arranged in two sub-series:
  Sub-series 1.1: A-Z files is arranged alphabetically by surname.
  Sub-series 1.2: Incomplete submissions is arranged alphabetically by surname.
  Scope and Contents
  Items in this series were originally housed in binders and organized by artists' surnames. Each file usually includes a resume, artist statement, and examples of artwork submitted by the artist to the registry. The submitted materials are mostly printed but occasionally appear on disks. Many submissions reference disks that were not included at the time of accession. Organizational histories reference an artists' slide registry, and although many files include slides, it's unclear if the slides were incorporated into these files or discarded after the slide registry digitization. The dates recorded for each file reflect the date of submission to the registry, not the dates of the artwork.
  - Sub-series 1.1: A-Z Files
    - Abdou, Irene, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abeler, Evi, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abergil, Inbal, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Abnous, Anet, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Abraham, Ellen, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Abrahamsson, Malin, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Abramovich, Daniel, circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Abrams, Rachel, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ahn, Jae Hi, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Ahn, Seongmin, circa 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Aige-Ventosa, Mar, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ainslie, Liz, circa 2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Albert, Caroline, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Albinowski, Yvonne, circa 2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alexander, Rahul, circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Alexandres, Stefan, circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Ford, circa 2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Allie, Fanny, circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alliegro, Anselmo, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alt, Ellen, circa 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Altamura, Mauro, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Alvanson, Kristen, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Amae, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Ambrosino, Guy, circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Amoros, Grimanesa, circa 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Anastasi, Audrey Frank, circa 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Anderson, Kristin, circa 2004 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Ando Stanoff, Miya, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Andrews, Jennifer, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Andro, Ginger and Glicksman, Chuck, circa 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Angelopoulos, Elaine, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Ansel, Eric, circa 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Apostolacus, Diane, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Arendt, Nicole, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Arinze, Samuel, circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Armbrust, Louisa, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Arvan, Mike, circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Aspenberg, Carla, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Assed, Barry, circa 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Associated Artists for Propaganda Research, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Avelluto, John, circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Augustine, Aliza, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Avi-Yonah, Yael, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ayanoglu, Mehmet, circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Azara, Nancy, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Back, Cynthia, circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Baen, Noah, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - de Bailliencourt, Agathe, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Baird, Kate, circa 2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Baker, Jessica, circa 2006 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Balakrishnan, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Ballengee, Brandon, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Baer, Ellen E., circa 2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Ban, Ju Young, circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Barker, Sarah, circa 2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Barnes, Julia Whitney, circa 2008 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Barnes, Patrick-Earl, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Barney, T., 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Barrack, Craig, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Barrett, Lori, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Bartlett, John W., 2009 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Bartlett, Melissa, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Basing, Hilary, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Bassis, Aileen, circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Bassman, Elliot, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Bauer, Jenna, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Baumfleck, David, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Beall, Karen Rich, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Beavers, Gina, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Beck, Michele, circa 2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Becker, Fred, circa 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Beckles, Ken, circa 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bejar, Daniel, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bellas, Benjamin, circa 2006 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Bello, Katrina, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Benarcik, Susan, circa 2010 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bendheim, Fred, circa 2007 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Benedis, Sheila, circa 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bereza, Sarah, circa 2005 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Bergeron, Rosie, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bergery, Nicholas, circa 2006 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Bergman, Dan, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Bergman Amarie, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bergman, Meredith Gang, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Bermudez, Sandra, circa 2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bernstein, Hal, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Bernstein, Marcia, circa 2008 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Bertiller, Gabriela, circa 2005 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Bessel, Eric, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Best, Tim, circa 2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Beuhler, Launa, circa 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Biehl, Katherine, circa 2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Biernoff, Elisheva, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Binzer, Mike, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Bird, Joel, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bisotto, Giacomo, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Bisson, Mariella, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Blas, Lisa, circa 2008 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Blackman, Jerry, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Block, Frieda, circa 2008 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Block, Tom, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bloise, Theresa, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Blue, Elise, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bluestone, Marissa, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Blum, Timothy, circa 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Blumberg, June, circa 2009 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bogaert, Tom, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bogatin, Anna, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Boggs, Tanya, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bojen, Anders, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Boker, Erik T., 2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Boland, Fletcher, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Boneham, Sunia, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Booth, Jennie, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Boram-Hays, Carol, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Borlandelli, Daniel, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Borshch, Dmitry, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Boudrot, Samantha, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Bouse, Amy, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Bowen, Dianne, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Bowen, Susan, circa 2009 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Bown, Dave, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Brahmst, Uli, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Brand, Jonathan, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Braun, Judith, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Brennan, Aillinn, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Brennan, Matthew M., 2008 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Brenneman Eno, Kristen, circa 2003 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Brenner, Beryl, circa 2009 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Brent, Adam, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Brewster, Jennilie, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Breyer, Nell, circa 2006 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Brilliant, Jonathan David, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bristow, Bethany, circa 2006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Brody-Lederman, Stephanie, circa 2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Brough, Helen, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Broughel, Suzanne, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Broussard, Matthew, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Deborah, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Brown, Jodi, circa 2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Brownell, Mia, circa 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Bruce, Daniel, circa 2007 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Bruno, Frank, circa 2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Buhmann, Stephanie, circa 2006 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Bunnycult, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Buono, Cat Del, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Buschur, Jordon, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Butler, Pam, circa 2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Byrne, Linda, circa 2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Byun, C Jae, circa 2008 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Cabbar, Ali, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Calder, Daniel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Calway-Fagen, Mike, circa 2007 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Campanella, Sparky, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Campbell, Bradley, circa 2004 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Campbell, Mary, circa 2006 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Cantela, Jeffery, circa 2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Capasso, Ariadna, circa 2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Cardwell, Pamela S., 2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Carpenter, Laurel, circa 2007 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Carr, Diane, circa 2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Carroll, Brendan, circa 2006 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Carter, Milton, circa 2006 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Casey, Jenny Zoe, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Cavazzi, Aimee, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Cecere, Jennifer, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cercone, Katie, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Chachitz, Jacqueline, circa 2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chan, Joyce, circa 2007 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Chapman, Thomas, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Chavez, Washington, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Chen, Gigi, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Childers, Travis, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Chin, Christine, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cho, Heejung, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cho, Yoon, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Choi, Hyung Sup, circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Chong, Cecile, circa 2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Chopra, Nikhill, circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Cichon, John, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Cirmo, Brian, circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Citrin, Ione, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Chambers, Christopher, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Giobbi, Chambliss, circa 2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Chan, Irene, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Chaiklin, Amy, circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Claire, Avy, circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Colon-Astacio, Mariestella, circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Confer, Alex, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Conforti, Michael, circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Conley, Jaclyn, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Conant, Chrissy, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Concannon, Leslie Farrell, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Connerton, Kim, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Connor, Annika, circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Conrad, Jillian, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Conroy, Juliette, circa 2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Cooper, Lilian, circa 2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Cooper, Pam, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Corio, Paul, circa 2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correia, Margarida, circa 2006 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Cortes S., Jose Luis, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Cossio, Angeles, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Cote, Andrea, circa 2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Crawford, Mark, circa 2007 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Creagh, Lisa, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Creighton, Lynn, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Cron, Claudia, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Cross, Veronica, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Crow, William, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Castro-Cruz Pedro, circa 2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cole Jr., Frank, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Colebrook, Ben, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Colon-Astacio, Mariestella, circa 2005 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Clark, Kate, circa 2007 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Close, Laurie, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Clovis, Donna, circa 2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Cocuzza, Julia, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Coe, Wayne, circa 2008 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Cubit, Carla, circa 2006 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Culbertson, Janet, circa 2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Cunningham, David, circa 2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Curtis, Joy, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Cutler, Rosie, circa 2007 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Cutter, Susan W., 2009 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Czacki, Chaterine, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Dade, Joyce, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Dahl, Lisa, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Dal Pra, Joseph, circa 2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Dalessandro, David, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Daniels, Katherine, circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Dann, Robin, circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Darcy, Brad William, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Daria, Voronina, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - D'Arpino, Evan, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Das, Reet, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Day, John, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Dearborn, Bridget, circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - DeAtley, Brantner, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - De Braud, Alberto, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - De Carvalho, Priscila, circa 2007 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Decker, Elisa, circa 2006 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Dee, Michael, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - DeFilippo, Christian, circa 2007 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Dembar, Seth, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - DeMyers, Theresa, circa 2006 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Denning, Sharon, circa 2003 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Denis, Craig, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - S. Deriso, Christopher, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Derwelis, Daniel, circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Desando, Sandra, circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - DesChene, Wendy, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - des Cognets, Nicholas, circa 2008 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - De Salvio, Theresa, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Desposito, Robyn, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Detrani, Geoffrey, circa 2007 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - De Vincentis, Mary, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - De Wald, Anthony Edwards, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - DeWald, Jenn, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Dick, Nico Pam, circa 2008 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Dickey, Patricia, circa 2006 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Didoardo, Mary, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Dillin, Lisa, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Dimov, Marc, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - DiPaola, Anthony, circa 2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dipaola, Marisa, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - DePasquale, David, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Djerejian, Madelin, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Dobill, Peter, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Dolgy Ludwig, Katherine, circa 2009 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Dombrowski, Bob, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Dombrowski, Terese, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Doret, Michael, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Dorman, Josh, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Dorsett, Stephen, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Douyon, Marie-Demise, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Doyle, Thomas, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Dreher, Damion, circa 2003 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Dreidemie, Carola, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Drendel, Kate, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Dreskin, Cybele, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Driscoll, Rolsalyn, circa 2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Drummond, Jeremy, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Duch, Tim, circa 1999 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Duehr, Gary, circa 2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Duffy, Mary Jane, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Dunaway, Leah, circa 2008 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Dunn, Richard, circa 2005 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Duran, Marco, circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Durbin, Paula, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Eappen, Roy, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Easton, Janae, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Eddleston, David, circa 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Edwards, Barbara, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Einstein, Ula, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Ellinger Smith, Katherine, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ellis, Loren, circa 2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ellmann, Barbara, circa 2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Elrod, Georgia, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Enright, Judy, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Enright, Nicky, circa 2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Entner, Benjamin, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Epstein, Mark, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Erickson, Josh, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ernst, Christopher, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Ernst, Matt, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ernst-Bifano, Sheila, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Estabrook, Mike, circa 2006 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Evans, Gregory C., circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ezer, Merav, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Fabian, Michael, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Faillace, Rachael, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Falby, Caroline, circa 2006 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Falchook, Jason, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Fancher, Bethany, circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Farranto, Emily, circa 2006 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Farrin, Laurel, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Faurot, Holly, circa 2006 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Fatta, Louis, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Fauvell, Kate C., 2009 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Feaster, Richard, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Fehrenbacher, Jill, circa 2004 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Fei, Cui, circa 2003 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Feld, Jeff, circa 2008 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Ferguson, Benjamin, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Ferguson, Jason, circa 2008 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ferguson, Laura, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Ferguson, Lisa, circa 2008 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Ferraro, Abraham, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)